[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["December 27th"]}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Does anyone still want the Trump seal of approval?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "anyone", "still", "want", "the", "Trump", "seal", "of", "approval", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "The debate is December 27th.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "debate", "is", "December", "27th", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Why is that and do you care?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "and", "do", "you", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, I don't really care, but I don't think I'm getting it too much.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "care", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "'m", "getting", "it", "too", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Did Mitt Romney call you himself to say he wasn't going to take part?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "Mitt", "Romney", "call", "you", "himself", "to", "say", "he", "was", "n't", "going", "to", "take", "part", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "And what did he -- what did he say?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "he", "--", "what", "did", "he", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, he couldn't have been nicer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "could", "n't", "have", "been", "nicer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "So you're not going to miss him kissing any part of your anatomy?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "miss", "him", "kissing", "any", "part", "of", "your", "anatomy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "No, I won't miss that at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "wo", "n't", "miss", "that", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What do you say to those critics in particular?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "those", "critics", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well, you have to understand, the reason I host \"Celebrity Apprentice\" and \"The Apprentice\" and it's become one of the top shows on television, and as you know, many nights, in fact, for a period of time, it was the number one show on television, and continues to get great ratings.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", "understand", ",", "the", "reason", "I", "host", "``", "Celebrity", "Apprentice", "''", "and", "``", "The", "Apprentice", "''", "and", "it", "'s", "become", "one", "of", "the", "top", "shows", "on", "television", ",", "and", "as", "you", "know", ",", "many", "nights", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "for", "a", "period", "of", "time", ",", "it", "was", "the", "number", "one", "show", "on", "television", ",", "and", "continues", "to", "get", "great", "ratings", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Do you find him funny?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "find", "him", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "I don't -- I think he's OK.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Newsmax"]}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "What do you think of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, first of all, the debate is a Newsmax debate and that's a very powerful organization, and they really are, and they've done an amazing job.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "the", "debate", "is", "a", "Newsmax", "debate", "and", "that", "'s", "a", "very", "powerful", "organization", ",", "and", "they", "really", "are", ",", "and", "they", "'ve", "done", "an", "amazing", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "What did you think of his point that he made?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "his", "point", "that", "he", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, I don't think he said it the way you said it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "said", "it", "the", "way", "you", "said", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "What do you think of that as a principle?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "as", "a", "principle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, he's really playing the class warfare very hard.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "really", "playing", "the", "class", "warfare", "very", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Is there a better way for him to say the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "better", "way", "for", "him", "to", "say", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, I think there are a lot of better ways.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "better", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Is there any momentum now building even slowly in the American economy, or is this false hope, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "momentum", "now", "building", "even", "slowly", "in", "the", "American", "economy", ",", "or", "is", "this", "false", "hope", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Well, I hope there's momentum.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "hope", "there", "'s", "momentum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "I mean, are you not genuinely tempted?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "you", "not", "genuinely", "tempted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, first of all, I never flirted many times.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "never", "flirted", "many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "And would it be fair to say that right now it would be pretty unthinkable that you would endorse anybody outside of Romney or Gingrich?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "it", "be", "fair", "to", "say", "that", "right", "now", "it", "would", "be", "pretty", "unthinkable", "that", "you", "would", "endorse", "anybody", "outside", "of", "Romney", "or", "Gingrich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Well, I don't want to say that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Would you consider being a vice president to any of these candidates?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "consider", "being", "a", "vice", "president", "to", "any", "of", "these", "candidates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "If one of these Republican candidates came to you and they became president next November, for argument's sake, and they said, look, Donald, we would like you to now be the trade negotiator for America, with China, with OPEC, and so on, would you take that job?", "question_tokens": ["If", "one", "of", "these", "Republican", "candidates", "came", "to", "you", "and", "they", "became", "president", "next", "November", ",", "for", "argument", "'s", "sake", ",", "and", "they", "said", ",", "look", ",", "Donald", ",", "we", "would", "like", "you", "to", "now", "be", "the", "trade", "negotiator", "for", "America", ",", "with", "China", ",", "with", "OPEC", ",", "and", "so", "on", ",", "would", "you", "take", "that", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, I certainly would consider that, because we need that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "would", "consider", "that", ",", "because", "we", "need", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "ORGANIZATION": ["OPEC"], "LOCATION": ["America", "China"], "PERSON": ["Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What do you think the key issues are?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "key", "issues", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, I think there are a lot of key issues.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "key", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "And you're going to give them a hard time, Donald, if they start taking you on and shirking the questions?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "give", "them", "a", "hard", "time", ",", "Donald", ",", "if", "they", "start", "taking", "you", "on", "and", "shirking", "the", "questions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "No, I don't think I -- look, first of all I know them.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "--", "look", ",", "first", "of", "all", "I", "know", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Do you like that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Well, if the title -- if the word Diva means hard work, a woman that knows what she wants, and won't take no for an answer, I don't mind being that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "the", "title", "--", "if", "the", "word", "Diva", "means", "hard", "work", ",", "a", "woman", "that", "knows", "what", "she", "wants", ",", "and", "wo", "n't", "take", "no", "for", "an", "answer", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "mind", "being", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "When do you really lose it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "you", "really", "lose", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I mean, I don't ask for much, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "ask", "for", "much", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What are the little things that can really drive you bonkers?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "little", "things", "that", "can", "really", "drive", "you", "bonkers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "If my dressing room is cold.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "my", "dressing", "room", "is", "cold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "How cold does it have to be before you explode?", "question_tokens": ["How", "cold", "does", "it", "have", "to", "be", "before", "you", "explode", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "If it's freezing, you know, if it's like super cold, uncomfortable.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "it", "'s", "freezing", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "it", "'s", "like", "super", "cold", ",", "uncomfortable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "What do you have to have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "have", "to", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I have to have lemon and honey.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "have", "lemon", "and", "honey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "What do Twizzlers do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "Twizzlers", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "NNP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, the licorice, it moistens your vocal chords.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "licorice", ",", "it", "moistens", "your", "vocal", "chords", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "So if I eat loads of Gummy Bears, would I suddenly get a huge voice like you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "if", "I", "eat", "loads", "of", "Gummy", "Bears", ",", "would", "I", "suddenly", "get", "a", "huge", "voice", "like", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Gummy Bears"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Is it that kind of thing that you crave?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "that", "you", "crave", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "It is very important.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "very", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Who are the people you think of first?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "people", "you", "think", "of", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "LIGE: My first thought is God, thank you, because without you, there is no people.", "answer_tokens": ["LIGE", ":", "My", "first", "thought", "is", "God", ",", "thank", "you", ",", "because", "without", "you", ",", "there", "is", "no", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "The individuals who have been there for you when it's really mattered?", "question_tokens": ["The", "individuals", "who", "have", "been", "there", "for", "you", "when", "it", "'s", "really", "mattered", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "I think about my mom, automatically.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "about", "my", "mom", ",", "automatically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "What were the values that meant most to her, do you think, that she instilled in you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "values", "that", "meant", "most", "to", "her", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "that", "she", "instilled", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "JJS", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "To be clean, to be clean, to keep our bodies clean, to wear clean underwear.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "be", "clean", ",", "to", "be", "clean", ",", "to", "keep", "our", "bodies", "clean", ",", "to", "wear", "clean", "underwear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What does she make of what you've achieved?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "make", "of", "what", "you", "'ve", "achieved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "My mom is very proud of me.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "mom", "is", "very", "proud", "of", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Or did she always think that she had a little live wire that had an amazing talent that may one day lead to this?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "did", "she", "always", "think", "that", "she", "had", "a", "little", "live", "wire", "that", "had", "an", "amazing", "talent", "that", "may", "one", "day", "lead", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "MD", "CD", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Well, she's not surprised.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "'s", "not", "surprised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "ORGAN: Are you shocked?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Are", "you", "shocked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "You know, I was.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Well, what feelings do you have to your father?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "feelings", "do", "you", "have", "to", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I love my dad.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "my", "dad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What was it like for you, at that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", ",", "at", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, it was exactly that, because I was making a turning point in my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "exactly", "that", ",", "because", "I", "was", "making", "a", "turning", "point", "in", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "``", "DT", "RBR", "NNP", "''", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "What was the tipping point for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "tipping", "point", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "The tipping point was during the \"No More Drama\" album -- that album cycle, because I feel that I had drank myself -- like that was it.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "tipping", "point", "was", "during", "the", "``", "No", "More", "Drama", "''", "album", "--", "that", "album", "cycle", ",", "because", "I", "feel", "that", "I", "had", "drank", "myself", "--", "like", "that", "was", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "But you felt you were going to die?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "felt", "you", "were", "going", "to", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yeah, so when it finally happened, I was like, wait a minute, this is not what I want.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "so", "when", "it", "finally", "happened", ",", "I", "was", "like", ",", "wait", "a", "minute", ",", "this", "is", "not", "what", "I", "want", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Who abused you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "abused", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "How much do you feel you owe Martin Kendu Isaacs, your husband now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "feel", "you", "owe", "Martin", "Kendu", "Isaacs", ",", "your", "husband", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I feel that I owe him my love.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "that", "I", "owe", "him", "my", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin Kendu Isaacs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "And your life, potentially?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "life", ",", "potentially", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "I don't owe him my life.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "owe", "him", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "When you look at what happened to Amy Winehouse, do you think that could have been you, if things had played out a different way for you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "look", "at", "what", "happened", "to", "Amy", "Winehouse", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "could", "have", "been", "you", ",", "if", "things", "had", "played", "out", "a", "different", "way", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy Winehouse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "When a moment for all African-Americans, I mean, around the world, never mine just America, right?", "question_tokens": ["When", "a", "moment", "for", "all", "African-Americans", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "around", "the", "world", ",", "never", "mine", "just", "America", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Did you talk to him, the president?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "talk", "to", "him", ",", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "What did you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "I said I love you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "I", "love", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "How do you think he's been dealing with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "been", "dealing", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "I think he's dealing with it pretty good, given the situation -- the situation he was put in and the mess that was thrown on him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "dealing", "with", "it", "pretty", "good", ",", "given", "the", "situation", "--", "the", "situation", "he", "was", "put", "in", "and", "the", "mess", "that", "was", "thrown", "on", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", ":", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Do you think, if given another chance, if he's re-elected, he can do perhaps what he wanted to do from the start but has been restricted from doing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", ",", "if", "given", "another", "chance", ",", "if", "he", "'s", "re-elected", ",", "he", "can", "do", "perhaps", "what", "he", "wanted", "to", "do", "from", "the", "start", "but", "has", "been", "restricted", "from", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I believe he's capable of doing -- of having another chance.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "he", "'s", "capable", "of", "doing", "--", "of", "having", "another", "chance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry David"]}, "docId": "111207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "On TV or whatever, who makes you laugh?", "question_tokens": ["On", "TV", "or", "whatever", ",", "who", "makes", "you", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Larry David makes me laugh.", "answer_tokens": ["Larry", "David", "makes", "me", "laugh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]